Connor Walden

Wingfield, 5013, SA | 0412248066

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/connor-walden-96122011b/

Personal Profile

Professional experience developing a salesforce product that empowers NDIS support providers. Ambition with a thirst for knowledge and learning. Easy-going yet able to handle stressful situations. Problem solver that applies critical thinking to find the source of issues and bugs. History building and maintaining computer hardware such as personal computers, laptops, servers and raspberry pi / arduino mini-robots.

Professional History

LABOURPOWER, Adelaide, South Australia

Pallet Repairer, Oct 2024 - Present

- Inspect softwood pallets for biological hazards such as termites and european house borers
- Use hand tools to pull broken boards off of pallets and reattach new boards
- Communicate effectively to ensure a smooth flow of product throughout the team
- Perform house-keeping duties such as machine operation checklists, resetting counters to manage throughput within the factory and keeping the work area tidy and clean at the end of shift so that the next shift can perform optimally.

ROBERTSON GLAZING, Adelaide, South Australia

Glazier, Nov 2023 - Oct 2024

TIPTOP BAKERIES, Adelaide, South Australia

Machine operator, rolls packing, Jan 2022 - Nov 2023

LUMARY, Adelaide, South Australia

Software Developer - Lumary Care Management, May 2021 - Nov 2022

- Use Kanban board to track the status of various jobs
- Refine work tickets and estimate their story points
- Timebox investigations into bugs to ensure efficiency
- Perform housekeeping for tickets in flight (Comment about why a ticket is in a certain column, validate pull request of tickets sitting in a ready to validate column, etc)
- Work in an agile sprint with all accompanying ceremonies (review, retrospective, planning)
- Use git / github for version control
- Make back end changes such to triggers, flows, selectors, unit tests and other apex code to ensure data is being interacted with properly
- Build front end components in AngularJS, lightning web components and visualforce.
- Configure developer, QA testing and production salesforce orgs
- Maintain at least a 75% test coverage. (Salesforce deployment requirement)

- Contribute to the design and implementation of the product via meetings and written proposals
- Be reactive to high severity bugs that are reported by customers
- Attend ad hoc and scheduled meetings.
- Attend meetings with customers to find pain points and quick wins, improving sentiment

Web development Certificate at Adelaide University (Dec 2020 - June 2021)

FURNITURE DESIGN AUSTRALIA, Adelaide, South Australia Workshop Assistant, Feb 2020 — Dec 2020

THE FUNDRAISING PEOPLE, Auckland, New Zealand Fundraiser, Nov 2019 — Jan 2019

CAPRAL ALUMINIUM, Angaston, South Australia Machine Operator, May 2019 — Nov 2019

COZWINE, Nuriootpa, South Australia Casual Factory Worker, Oct 2018 — Nov 2019

Education

UNIVERSITY OF ADELAIDE

Certificate of web development (MERN stack), Nov 2020 – Jun 2021 - Graduated

• TAFESA, Elizabeth, South Australia

Certificate 2 in Information, Digital Media and Technology, Aug 2017 - Jun 2018 - Graduated

Technical Skills

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES:

- Apex
- LWC
- Python
- JavaScript
- C++
- Java

Projects

My Portfolio – My portfolio that should be seen by all potential employers including all of my projects. Find it on github here: https://github.com/Connor-Walden/updated-portfolio Deployed URL: https://connor-walden.github.io/updated-portfolio/

References:

- **Matthew English**, CTO, Lumary Mobile: 0402 367 761 Email: matthew.english@lumary.com.au
- **Robert DeRosa**, Senior Developer, Lumary Mobile: 0431 378 422 Email: robert.derosa@lumary.com.au
- **Wagner Lopes**, Course Instructor, Adelaide University Mobile: 0451 631 417 Email: wagnerlopes.bh@gmail.com